{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Gianluigi3.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la meraviglia",
            "failed": 10,
            "lastAsked": 1492105620.3428867,
            "question": "Given the definition \"wonder, surprise\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sedersi",
            "failed": 11,
            "lastAsked": 1492105642.147083,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to set down\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 13
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il punteggio",
            "failed": 10,
            "lastAsked": 1492105599.400888,
            "question": "Given the definition \"score, points\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "even, also",
            "failed": 13,
            "lastAsked": 1492105586.1057298,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"persino\"?",
            "tried": 16
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "alzarsi",
            "failed": 12,
            "lastAsked": 1492105734.320753,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to get up\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 14
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "still"
            ],
            "answer": "still, yet",
            "failed": 17,
            "lastAsked": 1492105758.4471598,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ancora\"?",
            "tried": 20
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "therefore",
                "well, therefore"
            ],
            "answer": "therefore, well",
            "failed": 17,
            "lastAsked": 1492105711.88466,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"dunque\"?",
            "tried": 21
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "persino",
            "failed": 15,
            "lastAsked": 1492105749.6515794,
            "question": "Given the definition \"even, also\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 18
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "prendere",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1487598964.6925044,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to take (in)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fare finta di",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1492105889.5131125,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to pretend\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "often",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492105884.5908313,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"spesso\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'aranciata",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1492105817.6236033,
            "question": "Given the definition \"orange drink\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "il frigorifero"
            ],
            "answer": "il frigorifero (frigo)",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492105881.2775104,
            "question": "Given the definition \"refrigerator\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ace",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1492105820.9368465,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'asso\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "riunirsi",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492105894.7863483,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to get together\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to get up",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1487097925.5928152,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"alzarsi\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to discover",
                "to find out"
            ],
            "answer": "to find out, discover",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1487598912.1891904,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"scoprire\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "un'altra volta",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1487599115.721704,
            "question": "Given the definition \"again, another time\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "intruso",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487097428.7177608,
            "question": "Given the definition \"intruded\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "dunque",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487096912.875075,
            "question": "Given the definition \"therefore, well\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "wonder, surprise",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487097683.2101164,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la meraviglia\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "queen in cards",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487097357.7513175,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il fante\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to pretend",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487098096.4217744,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"fare finta di\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "scoprire",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487098244.3715725,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to find out, discover\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "intruded",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487096996.6293433,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"intruso\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il fante",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487097088.7359087,
            "question": "Given the definition \"queen in cards\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "player",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487097353.077307,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il giocatore\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ancora",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1487598980.6635985,
            "question": "Given the definition \"still, yet\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "already",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487098233.316295,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"gia\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il re",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487097359.783165,
            "question": "Given the definition \"king\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la cannuccia",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1487599044.3103397,
            "question": "Given the definition \"drinking straw\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "contare",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487096842.8325248,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to count\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il papa",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487096907.1190152,
            "question": "Given the definition \"father\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "raccongliere",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487097871.090224,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to pick up, collect\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "osservare",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487096991.8697972,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to observe\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "arrabbiarsi",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487097422.9495554,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to get angry\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il gioco",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487097536.915617,
            "question": "Given the definition \"game\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to take (in)",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487097349.6593533,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"prendere\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'inizio",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487098111.0893848,
            "question": "Given the definition \"the beginning\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "piu'",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1487096994.2133908,
            "question": "Given the definition \"more\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "le carte",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487097852.8463216,
            "question": "Given the definition \"playing cards\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "dinner",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487097073.52056,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il pranzo\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "gia",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487098231.0996284,
            "question": "Given the definition \"already\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "game",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487097405.1065476,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il gioco\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "chiudere",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487096889.9677062,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to close\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "in pensione",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487097858.8259256,
            "question": "Given the definition \"retired\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il giocatore",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487097979.5519338,
            "question": "Given the definition \"player\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "creare",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487096988.0857205,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to create\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "To get together"
            ],
            "answer": "to get together",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487096834.913132,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"riunirsi\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "spesso",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487097653.5902045,
            "question": "Given the definition \"often\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "gli zii",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487097165.9060202,
            "question": "Given the definition \"aunts and uncles\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to get dressed",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487097910.0054178,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"vestirsi\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the score"
            ],
            "answer": "score, points",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487097085.416409,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il punteggio\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "popolare",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487096966.5141854,
            "question": "Given the definition \"popular\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "drinking straw",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487096974.0096064,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la cannuccia\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il proprietario",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487098215.8313422,
            "question": "Given the definition \"owner, proprieter\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "tardi",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487097919.6249547,
            "question": "Given the definition \"late\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "the beginning",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487097913.8009088,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'inizio\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sapere",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487096820.8411274,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to know how, a fact\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "di tanto in tanto",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487097515.5122654,
            "question": "Given the definition \"every now & then\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to know how, fact"
            ],
            "answer": "to know how, a fact",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487097511.8247108,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"sapere\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'appetito",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487097071.264942,
            "question": "Given the definition \"appetite, hunger\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "gli uomini",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487098084.0453472,
            "question": "Given the definition \"men\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "Certo!",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487096892.7832415,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Of course!\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "proprieter"
            ],
            "answer": "owner, proprieter",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487097065.22062,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il proprietario\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il mazzo di carte",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1487096818.5051942,
            "question": "Given the definition \"deck of cards\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "dormire",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097930.4170907,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to sleep\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "uomo"
            ],
            "answer": "l'uomo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097364.7989237,
            "question": "Given the definition \"man\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "popular",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487096853.6962144,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"popolare\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to count",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487096953.1830196,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"contare\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "playing cards",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097849.4063807,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"le carte\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "Of course!",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097596.3304415,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Certo!\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "men",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487096932.9589603,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"gli uomini\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'asso",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097933.6573539,
            "question": "Given the definition \"ace\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "king",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097958.7162416,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il re\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "from time to time"
            ],
            "answer": "every now & then",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097030.1692147,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"di tanto in tanto\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "late",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487096998.605599,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"tardi\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "cavallo"
            ],
            "answer": "il cavallo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097906.7813697,
            "question": "Given the definition \"horse\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "enter"
            ],
            "answer": "to enter",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097051.5493174,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"entrare\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "eliminate"
            ],
            "answer": "to eliminate",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097370.199035,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"eliminare\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "entrare",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097846.030215,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to enter\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il nonno",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487098012.5714316,
            "question": "Given the definition \"grandfather\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "deck of cards",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487096800.4773166,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il mazzo di carte\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "pranzo"
            ],
            "answer": "il pranzo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097322.1519399,
            "question": "Given the definition \"dinner\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the man"
            ],
            "answer": "man",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097445.7296865,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'uomo\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to get angry",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097880.6256576,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"arrabbiarsi\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vestirsi",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097901.7813768,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to get dressed\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "grandpa"
            ],
            "answer": "grandfather",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097131.0716944,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il nonno\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "appetite"
            ],
            "answer": "appetite, hunger",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097374.6073055,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'appetito\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "giocare",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097469.1890259,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to play a sport, cards\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to play"
            ],
            "answer": "to play a sport, cards",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097949.3885217,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"giocare\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "orange drink",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487098179.3567176,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'aranciata\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to create",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097604.9188924,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"creare\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "horse",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097091.8480055,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il cavallo\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to set down",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097937.0569303,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"sedersi\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to eat",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487096776.689725,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"mangiare\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "retired",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097811.8909132,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"in pensione\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "refrigerator",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487096774.185673,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il frigorifero (frigo)\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to collect, to pick up"
            ],
            "answer": "to pick up, collect",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097944.0283616,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"raccongliere\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "mangiare",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097307.5923169,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to eat\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "observe"
            ],
            "answer": "to observe",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097326.5518641,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"osservare\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the father"
            ],
            "answer": "father",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097402.5790403,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il papa\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "aunts and uncles",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097889.2615616,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"gli zii\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to be able to do"
            ],
            "answer": "to be able, can",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487098025.9511163,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"potere\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "eliminare",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487096789.7976658,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to eliminate\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to sleep",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097113.1718955,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"dormire\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "more",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097808.8751955,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"piu'\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "potere",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097310.0721955,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be able, can\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to close",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487097829.978758,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"chiudere\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "another time"
            ],
            "answer": "again, another time",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1487096866.0282235,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"un'altra volta\"?",
            "tried": 1
        }
    ]
}